

## **USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER**

US / +1 808 319-0008 reed.megan.n@gmail.com www.meganreed.com

### PERSONAL STATEMENT

I create user-driven design solutions while understanding the nuances of the user/guest experience that are unique to the hospitality & travel industry.

10+ years of experience across the spectrum of UX, UI & Digital Product Design with multi-cultural teams around the world.

Advocate of the user. Designer of experiences & interfaces.

# **PROJECTS & UX TOOLSET**

### **UpStay, MOBILE APP & WEBSITE**

UX/UI and Mobile App Design for on-demand booking of hotel services, completing the entire design cycle.

### UX Process & Tools Used in Project:

- Ideation & Conceptual Design
- User Centered Design Methodology
- · Rapid Wireframing & Prototyping
- Mobile App UI Design
- HCI Methods
- GitHub Collaboration
- Front-End Dev: HTML & CSS

# SommMe, MOBILE APP

Mobile application using chatbot interactions to provide wine pairing recommendations to users.

### Additional UX Process & Tools Used:

- Chatbot Interaction Design
- User Stories & Personas
- Branding & Identity
- · Information Architecture
- InVision Clickable Prototyping
- Sketch App Design
- Adobe Illustrator Logo Design

### myStamford, WEB APP & WEBSITE

Communication platform built with user-centered design methodology and extensive user research process.

# Additional UX Process & Tools Used:

- UX Research & Strategy
- User Surveys & Interviews
- · Creative Direction
- Content Management
- Usability Testing (1:1 & Remote)

# WORK EXPERIENCE

## MIAMI, USA **EXPERIENCE DESIGNER**

EVERYBELL | 2014 - Current

- Utilizes an agile, user-centered design methodology to lead UX and product design on all products including mobile & web apps and website.
- Conceptualizes and designs brand identity from a holistic point of view, setting up design patterns to ensure consistency across product family.
- Designs and facilitates executive level presentations, securing key partnerships with major hotel brands and key hotel management groups.
- Leads user research, product idea generation, conceptual prototyping; executing design deliverables for user-centered service product.
- Executes email marketing campaigns with focus on optimization, content creation, analytics to effectively measure and focus on high-impact activities.

# SINGAPORE SENIOR MANAGER, MARKETING & PRODUCT

STAMFORD | 2013 - 2014

- Creative direction from concept to launch for new digital and print marketing campaign resulting in 600% growth year-over year.
- Managed entire UX design cycle for new user-driven digital product design, seeing an increase in client engagement and retention of 65% after launch.
- Set product vision, assigned tasks to on-site and remote team of designers and developers to redesign website optimized for social media, analytics, SEO.
- Planned, promoted, executed high-profile event bringing \$250K media value.

## SINGAPORE CORPORATE MARKET MANAGER, APAC

HRS HOTEL PORTAL | 2011 - 2013

- Led multi-national team to secure valuable corporate partnerships in the region to achieve successful corporate expansion from Germany to APAC.
- Increased hotel booking by 40% in the region through generating corporate client agreements of up to \$2M of revenue per campaign.
- Assisted product management to improve functionality of training platform for on-boarding of B2B clients through ensuring usability and understanding dependencies on other internal apps.
- Collaborated with Executive team to redesign corporate presentation used in strategic development for hotel and corporate acquisition.

## HAWAII, USA GUEST EXPERIENCE LEAD

FOUR SEASONS HOTELS | 2009 - 2010

- Provided Executive committee with guest experience recommendations and insights for \$1M concept redesign for fine-dining restaurant.
- Collaborated to deliver menu and product design deliverables for new concept; recognized as #1 Big Island Restaurant and #1 Fine Dining Restaurant in Hawaii.
- Facilitated high-value guest experience interaction to inform insights for service standards and improve feedback and overall outlet rankings.
- Strategized promotional events to drive traffic, brand awareness, loyalty.

# HAWAII, USA DENVER, USA

RECRUITMENT & OPERATIONS LEAD
TERRITORY MARKETING REPRESENTATIVE

YWAM | 2007 - 2009 INTUIT | 2006

## **EDUCATION**

UX/UI DESIGN & FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT B.S. BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, MARKETING

Bloc.io | 2016 - 2017

Colorado Christian University | 2002 - 2006